<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#353535"
    tools:context=".TermsOfServiceActivity">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView19"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Terms and conditions"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView39"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text='These terms and conditions ("Terms", "Agreement") are an agreement between Mobile Application Developer ("Mobile Application Developer", "us", "we" or "our") and you ("User", "you" or "your"). This Agreement sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the Greenmap mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, "Mobile Application" or "Services").'
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView74"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Accounts and membership"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView75"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review new accounts before you may sign in and use our Services. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. We may suspend, disable, or delete your account (or any part thereof) if we determine that you have violated any provision of this Agreement or that your conduct or content would tend to damage our reputation and goodwill. If we delete your account for the foregoing reasons, you may not re-register for our Services. We may block your email address and Internet protocol address to prevent further registration. "
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView76"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="User content"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView77"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text='We do not own any data, information or material ("Content") that you submit in the Mobile Application in the course of using the Service. You shall have sole responsibility for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, appropriateness, and intellectual property ownership or right to use of all submitted Content. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review Content in the Mobile Application submitted or created using our Services by you. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the Mobile Application does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the Content created by you or stored in your user account for commercial, marketing or any similar purpose. But you grant us permission to access, copy, distribute, store, transmit, reformat, display and perform the Content of your user account solely as required for the purpose of providing the Services to you. Without limiting any of those representations or warranties, we have the right, though not the obligation, to, in our own sole discretion, refuse or remove any Content that, in our reasonable opinion, violates any of our policies or is in any way harmful or objectionable. '
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView78"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Backups"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView79"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="We perform regular backups of the  Content, however, these backups are for our own administrative purposes only and are in no way guaranteed. You are responsible for maintaining your own backups of your data. We do not provide any sort of compensation for lost or incomplete data in the event that backups do not function properly. We will do our best to ensure complete and accurate backups, but assume no responsibility for this duty."
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView80"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Prohibited uses"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView81"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="In addition to other terms as set forth in the Agreement, you are prohibited from using the Mobile Application or its Content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; (c) to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Service or of any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet; (h) to collect or track the personal information of others; (i) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (j) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (k) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Service or any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet. We reserve the right to terminate your use of the Service or any related mobile application for violating any of the prohibited uses."
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView82"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Intellectual property rights"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView83"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="This Agreement does not transfer to you any intellectual property owned by Mobile Application Developer or third-parties, and all rights, titles, and interests in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Mobile Application Developer. All trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with our Mobile Application or Services, are trademarks or registered trademarks of Mobile Application Developer or Mobile Application Developer licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with our Mobile Application or Services may be the trademarks of other third-parties. Your use of our Mobile Application and Services grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any Mobile Application Developer or third-party trademarks. "
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView84"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Changes and amendments"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView85"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Mobile Application or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will post a notification in our Mobile Application. Continued use of the Mobile Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. Policy was created with https://www.WebsitePolicies.com "
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView86"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Acceptance of these terms"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView87"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services."
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView88"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text=" This document was last updated on April 18, 2020"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="#F4F4F4" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>